The magic is back again!
Lethal Weapon 3 is a action, comedy, thriller film directed by Richard Donner.
Riggs and Murtaugh pursue a former officer who uses his knowledge of police procedure and
policies to steal and sell confiscated guns and ammunition to local street gangs.
Martin Riggs, played by Mel Gibson.
Roger Murtaugh, played by Danny Glover.
Leo Getz, played by Joe Pesci.
Lorna Cole, played by Rene Russo.
Jack Travis, played by Stuart Wilson.
Captain Murphy, played by Steve Kahan.
Lethal Weapon 3 is a 1992 American buddy cop action film directed by Richard
Donner and written by Jeffrey Boam and Robert Mark Kamen.
The sequel to Lethal Weapon 2 (1989), it is the third installment in the Lethal Weapon film
series and stars Mel Gibson, Danny Glover, Joe Pesci, Rene Russo, and Stuart Wilson.
In Lethal Weapon 3, LAPD Sergeants Martin Riggs (Gibson) and Roger Murtaugh (Glover) pursue Jack Travis (Wilson), a
former LAPD lieutenant turned ruthless arms dealer, during the six days prior to Murtaugh's retirement.
Riggs and Murtaugh are joined by Leo Getz (Pesci) as well as
internal affairs Sergeant Lorna Cole (Russo).
The film was a box office success, grossing over $320 million worldwide.
It was the fifth-highest-grossing film of 1992 and the
highest-grossing installment in the series overall.
The film was followed by Lethal Weapon 4 in 1998.
The film explores themes of showdown, police, sequel, mixed
martial arts (mma), los angeles, california.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.